A Guide to the Secretary of Administration, Records, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Secretary of Administration, Records, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
38941
17.23 cubic feet (18 boxes).
Transferred from Office of the Secretary of Administration, January 10, 2002.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected information closed for 100 years after date record created. Types of records restricted include, but are not limited to: state employee/dependent medical information, employee performance reviews, and employee grievance materials that were sent to the Secretary of Administration and are part of the constituent correspondence series. Death certificates are closed for 50 years and are also found within the constituent correspondence series. Attorney-Client privileged documents are closed permanently.
Access to architectural and engineering plans and drawings of current governmental buildings requires a written request from the prospective user and written authorization from the appropriate authority with the agency occupying the facility.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Secretary of Administration on January 10, 2002.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Office of Administration was established in 1966 as part of the Office of the Governor to assist the chief executive in carrying out his duties. Several agencies including the divisions of the Budget, Personnel, Engineering and Building and Planning reported to the Commissioner of Administration. This system was inadequate. In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governors top management team or "secretariats," as they are called now.
Governor Linwood Holton's top priority for the 1972 session of the General Assembly was a proposal for a Governor's Cabinet, reorganizing state agencies into six major departments--each headed by a secretary appointed by the governor. The Office of Administration was made one of these six departments. The office of Secretary of Administration was created on April 8, 1972, by an act passed by the General Assembly. Governor Holton appointed T. Edward Temple, the Commissioner of Administration since 1970, as the first Secretary of Administration. When Temple took office on July 1, 1972, he was responsible for the divisions of the Budget, Personnel, Engineering and Buildings, Automated Data Processing, Justice and Crime Prevention, State Planning and Community Affairs, Council on the Environment, State Board of Elections and the Office of Special Programs. The Office has undergone a series of administrative reorganizations since 1972. On April 12, 1976, the Legislature combined the secretariats for administration and finance, effective July 1, 1976. On July 1, 1984, the offices were separated. The Secretary of Administration is a member of the Governor's Cabinet, and is appointed by the governor, subject to confirmation by the General Assembly. Currently the Secretary of Administration is responsible for the direction or jurisdiction over the following state agencies and boards: Charitable Gambling Commission, Compensation Board, Department of Employee Relations Counselors, Department of General Services, Department of Human Resource Management, Council on Human Rights, Commission on Local Government, Department of Rights for Virginians with Disabilities, and the Department of Veteran's Affairs.
In January 1998 Governor-elect James S. Gilmore III named G. Bryan Slater as Secretary of Administration. Slater also served as Gilmore's Deputy Chief of Staff. He worked on Gilmore's campaign for attorney general in 1993 and served as his director of administration when Gilmore was Virginia Attorney General (1994-1997). Slater resigned in March 2001 to work for the Republican National Committee which Gilmore chaired. He was replaced by his deputy, Donald L. Moseley who served until the end of the Gilmore administration in January 2002.
Scope and Content Information
The Secretary of Administration records contain 17.23 cubic feet of material ranging from 1998-2001 (with a few items dating from 1990-1997) and are arranged in sixteen series. Series I consists of constituent correspondence to the Governor referred to the secretary for response and are arranged by tracking numbers assigned by the Governor's Office and date received. The majority of the correspondence are from state employees and veterans and describe their concerns. G. Bryan Slater, Secretary of Administration, or Donald L. Moseley, wrote responses to nearly all of these letters. Series II is correspondence to the Office of the Secretary and is arranged chronologically. Series III contains correspondence arranged by department and then chronologically therein. Notable topics include State Board of Election material related to the Motor Voter Program. Series IV and V consists of records related to capital expenditures and state maintenance are arranged by subject.
Series VI contains Environmental Impact Studies for state funded construction projects and are arranged by date of approval by the Secretary of Administration. Series VII consists of Legislative Files containing Enrolled Bill Reviews and Legislative Action Summaries on bills pertaining to the Secretary of Administration. The Secretary reviewed these documents, added his comments and sent his recommendation to the Governor. Series VII also includes some Department of Planning and Budget Fiscal Impact Statements and talking points prepared for the Secretary.
Series VIII contains minutes and transcripts of the Public Broadcast Board from 1998 to 2001. Series IX documents Governor Gilmore's Town Hall meetings with state employees held in September 1998 including the Governor's briefing book, employee comment cards and videotapes of all four meetings. Series IX also includes a complete statistical report on the 1998 state employee survey. Series X consists of the records of the Y2K Project Office (also known as the Century Date Change Initiative Project Office) containing correspondence, minutes, notes and reports. Series XI and XII chronicle special projects undertaken by the secretary involving the 2000 census and military voting. Series XIII contains intellectual property reports from 1995 to 2001. Series XIV consists of assessments of state and federal mandates on state agencies and local governments. Series XV documents the transfer of Richmond's Main Street Station to the City of Richmond.
Series XVI chronicles the 1998-2000 renovation of the Executive Mansion. The series is divided into seven sub-series: Studies, Electronic Mail, Organizations, Project Records, Articles, Miscellaneous and Bob Vila. Included is a copy of 1990 study titled "Long Range Improvement Planning Study for the Executive Mansion, Capitol Square, Richmond, Virginia." The electronic mail sub-series contains messages either written to, written by or cc to G. Bryan Slater between 1998-2000. Notable recipients/writers include: Billy Reid, Special Assistant, Office of the Secretary of Administration; Donald C. Williams, Director of the Department of General Services; Donna Case, Director of the Executive Mansion; Roxanne G. Gilmore, First Lady of Virginia; Sarah Beaseley Monzon of Bob Vila Television; and Samuel W. Daniel, construction manager. Subjects include: mansion renovation brochure; Architectural Digest article; punch-list items, repairs and to-do lists; media request to tour the mansion; Bob Vila/Home Again filming; move back to the mansion; progress reports on mansion work; and the move to the Brown home. Notable message include: a 19 June 2000 e-mail from Donna Case, relaying Roxanne Gilmore's concerns about the mansions bug problems; a 29 December 1999 message from Billy Reid relaying Bob Vila's request that he be flown from Boston to Richmond then to Miami on the state plane; and a 18 October 1999 message from Donald C. Williams describing a meeting Williams had with Samuel Daniel about the projects schedule.
The sub-series Project Records contains a wealth of information on the renovation including: Executive Committee minutes, agenda and reports from 1998-1999; documents describing the search for temporary housing for the governor while the renovations are taking place; punch-lists from 1999-2000 documenting various minor problems/repairs that need to be made to the Executive Mansion and newspaper and magazine articles about the renovation.
The sub-series on Bob Vila contains correspondence and newspaper clippings on Vila's documentation of the renovation project for his program Bob Vila's Home Again. Videotapes of all thirteen episodes are included.
Organization
Organized into the following series: Series I. Constituent Correspondence; Series II. Correspondence - Office of the Secretary; Series III. Correspondence - State Agencies; Series IV. Capital Outlay Files; Series V. Maintenance Files; Series VI. Environmental Impact Studies; Series VII. Legislative Files; Series VIII. Public Broadcasting Board Minutes
Series IX. Town Hall Meeting Files/State Employee Survey and Results Data; Series X. Y2K Project Office Files; Series XI. Census Project; Series XII. Military Voting Project; Series XIII. Intellectual Property Reports; Series XIV. Assessment of State and Federal Mandates on Local Government; Series XV. Main Street Station; Series XVI. Executive Mansion Renovation
Contents List
- Constituent Correspondence 1998-2001
  Chronological by tracking number.
  - Correspondence Numbers 146-1203 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Numbers 1315-3897 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Numbers 3983-13651 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Numbers 16127-24922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Numbers 25374-28238 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Numbers 28346-30831 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Numbers 30910-32940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Numbers 32976-34835 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Numbers 34852-38014 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Numbers 35485-49060 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Numbers 49062-51940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Numbers 51964-55236 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Numbers 55442-58286 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Numbers 58299-62584 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Numbers 66622-66838 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Numbers 67196-68348 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Numbers 68377-69412 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence Numbers 69432-72995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence Numbers 73396-75957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence Numbers 76863-77816 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Numbers 77940-80065 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Numbers 80072-83291 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Numbers 83529-85954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Numbers 86082-92085 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Numbers 92172-93303 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Numbers 93436-95922 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Numbers 96451-98394 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Numbers 98449-100907 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Numbers 1010044-102153 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Numbers 102234-103915 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Numbers 103935-105296 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Numbers 105305-107379 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Numbers 107424-110182 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Numbers 110314-111554 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Numbers 111601-200403 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Numbers 200628-203455 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence Numbers 204005-2006272 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2006595-2010829 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence Numbers 201407-2014338 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2014443-2016594 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2014088-2028035 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2028059-2032141 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2032312-2033922 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2033924-2035740 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2035769-2037881 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2037883-2039778 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2039713-2040521 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2040528-2044187 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2044302-2052733 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2052894-2062523 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2062810-2068825 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2068835-2073344 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2073424-2077793 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2077796-2081602 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2081637-2084721 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2084735-2087578 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Numbers 2087612-2088613 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Correspondence - Office of the Secretary 1998-2001
  Chronological.
  - January - June 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - July - December 1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1999 - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - State Agencies
  - Charitable Gambling Commission, January - June 1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Charitable Gambling Commission, July - December 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Charitable Gambling Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Compensation Board, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Department of Employee Relations Counselors, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Department of General Services, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Department of General Services, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Department of General Services, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Department of Human Resource Management, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Department of Human Resource Management, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Department of Human Resource Management, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Council on Human Rights, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Local Government, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Department for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Department for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Department of Veterans' Affairs, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Veterans Care Center, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Care Center, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Care Center - Videotape (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Care Center - Wandergarden (Alzheimer's Addition) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - State Board of Elections, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - State Board of Elections - Subject Files (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - State Board of Elections - Subject Files (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Motor Voter Program Records - Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Motor Voter Program Records - Review of the State Board of Elections, Exposure Draft of JLARC report, 23 October 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Motor Voter Program Records - VVRS Study Committee Report, December 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Motor Voter Program Records - VVRS Study Committee Reports, December 1999 and October 2000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Capital Outlay Files
  - Chronological correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chronological correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Blue Ridge Hospital Property (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cheatham Annex Fuel Depot, York County (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - D-Day Memorial, Bedford, Virginia (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Greensprings Property, Louisa County (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Holocaust Museum (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Virginia State Police - Statewide Shared Land Mobile Radio System (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Virginia War Memorial - Carillon (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Real Property Files, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Real Property Files, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Maintenance Files
  - Bell Tower (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Veterans Cemetery (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Virginia War Memorial (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Environmental Impact Studies 1998-2001
  - 23 January 1998 - 11 March 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 12 March 1998 - 5 June 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 9 June 1998 - 28 July 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 29 July 1998 - 7 October 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 14 October 1998 - 13 November 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 19 November 1998 - 1 February 1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 3 February 1999 - 25 March 1999 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 2 April 1999 - 24 May 1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 27 May 1999 - 28 June 1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 9 July 1999 - 17 August 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 20 August 1999 - 9 September 1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 23 September 1999 - 29 October 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 2 November 1999 - 3 December 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 9 December 1999 - 24 January 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1 February 2000 - 30 March 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 11 April 2000 - 31 May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 9 June 2000 - 13 July 2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 25 July 2000 - 25 September 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 2 October 2000 - 6 November 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 14 November 2000 - 18 December 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 8 January 2001 - 9 February 2001 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 12 February 2001 - 9 March 2001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 26 March 2001 - 2 May 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 7 May 2001 - 8 June 2001 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 15 June 2001 - 16 July 2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 18 July 2001 - 7 August 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 20 August 2001 - 27 September 2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 5 October 2001 - 2 November 2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 7 November 2001 - 13 December 2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Legislative Files 1998-2001
  - 1998 Session
    - House 1998; HB 20 - HB 37 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 41 - HB 271 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 272 - HB 591 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 610 - HB 1079 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 1082 - HB 1411; SB 2 - SB 11 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - SB 13 - SB 322 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - SB 343 - SB 718 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1999 Session
    - 1999 Index; HB 189 - HB 1467 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - HB 1475 - HB 1610 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - HB 1612 - HB 1692 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - HB 1700 - HB 1805 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - HB 1806 - HB 1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - HB 1970 - HB 2132 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - HB 2138 - HB 2413 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - HB 2451 - HB 2759; SB 220 - SB 728 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - SB 730 - SB 831 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - SB 832 - SB 1122 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - SB 1123 - SB 1287 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 2000 Session
    - HB 4 - HB 71 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - HB 79 - HB 135 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - HB 142 - HB 209 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - HB 211 - HB 398 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - HB 399 - HB 470 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - HB 491 - HB 494 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - HB 510 - HB 611 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - HB 622 - HB 690 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - HB 693 - HB 811 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - HB 813 - HB 855 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - HB 858 - HB 1007 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - HB 1036 - HB 1124 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - HB 1136 - HB 1163 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - HB 1177 - HB 1209 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - HB 1233 - HB 1304 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - HB 1327 - HB 1385 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - HB 1395 - HB 1497 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - HB 1511 - HB 1534; HJ 01 - HJ 280 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - SJ 38 - SJ 252 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - SB 1 - SB 59 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SB 67 - SB 205 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SB 221 - SB 285 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SB 315 - SB 383 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SB 388 - SB 419 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SB 420 - SB 441 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SB 454 - SB 538 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - SB 541 - SB 555 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - SB 579 - SB 639 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - SB 656 - SB 709 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - SB 713 - SB 732 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - SB 735 - SB 780 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 2001 Session
    Chronological by date Secretary of Administration reviewed legislation.
    - 25 January 2001 - 26 February 2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 27 February 2001 - 28 February 2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 1 March 2001 - 2 March 2001 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 7 March 2001 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - 8 March 2001 (Box 10a, Folder 1)
    - March 2001 and Special Session (Box 10a, Folder 2)
- Public Broadcasting Board Minutes 1998-2001
  - Minutes of 1998 meetings (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of 17 February 1999 meeting (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of 10 June 1999 meeting (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Transcript of 6 August 1999 meeting (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Transcript of 1 September 1999 meeting (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Minutes of 17 February 2000 meeting (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Transcript of 4 May 2000 meeting (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Transcript of 24 May 2000 meeting (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of 6 September 2000 meeting (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and Transcript of 27 September 2000 meeting (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Transcript of 13 December 2000 meeting (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and Transcript of 21 February 2001 meeting (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and Transcript of 9 May 2001 meeting (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Agency Employees on Temporary Assignment and 30-Day Extensions, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Town Hall Meetings and State Employee Survey 1998-1999
  - Town Hall Meeting Files - 1998
    - Planning/Schedule of Meetings (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Cabinet Secretary's Briefing Book (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Press Office - News Briefs for 24-27 September 1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Card Responses - Secretary of Administration (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Card Responses - Secretary of Public Safety (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Card Responses - Other cabinet secretaries (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Card Responses - Office of the Governor (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Employee Town Hall Comment Cards (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Videotape of Roanoke Town Hall Meeting - 23 September 1998 (2 copies) (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Videotape of Annandale Town Hall Meeting - 24 September 1998 (2 copies) (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Videotape of Norfolk Town Hall Meeting - 24 September 1998 (2 copies) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Videotape of Richmond Town Hall Meeting - 25 September 1998 (2 copies) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - State Employee Survey and Results Data, 1998-1999
    - Preliminary Data Tables (October - November 1998) (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 1, Table 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 1, Table 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 1, Table 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 1, Table 4 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 2, Table 5 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 2, Table 6 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 2, Table 7 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 2, Table 8 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 2, Table 9 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Final Data Tables (12 December 1998), Volume 2, Table 10 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Governor's Briefing - 15 January 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Survey Results - released 28 April 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)